Phone: 737-491-006 Address: Traugutta 77C, Czestochowa, Poland

E-mail: karol@kedzia.pl Date of birth: 21.03.1986

# Karol Kędzia

Effective Manager with a rich knowledge of e-commerce, e-grocery, FMCG. IT engineer. Network administration specialist. Certified software tester according to the ISTQB certification. Beginner Front – End Developer. Perfect organizer, focused on improving sales processes, logistics and operability. Emotionally intelligent employee.

More information about my person: http://karol-kedzia.pl



## **EDUCATION:**

2011 - 2015



www.wsei.edu.pl

**Higher School of Economics and Computer Science in Cracow** *Bachelor of Engineering* - Information Technology and Econometrics,
Computer Network Administration,

# **CERTIFICATES, SKILLS AND ABILITIES:**



www.istgb.org

- ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level Certificate,
- ISTQB Foundation Level Certificate of Completion,
- "Selenium WebDriver" Test Automation Certificate of Completion,
- Front End Developer Certificate of Completion,
- Driving License,

# **EXPERIENCE:**

2012-10 -



www.vet-shop.pl

# Vet-Shop.pl - ESKULAP, Cracow

E-commerce Manager

- managing and leading online store Vet-Shop.pl,
- control of sales processes and the course of orders realization,
- coordination, control, updating inventory and bids retail store,
- implementation of sales plans,
- maintaining good relationships with trading partners, including the main strategic partner Royal Canin Poland,
- personnel management, organization of employees working time,
- running advertising campaigns
- bookkeeping,

2011-04 - 2012-07



www.a.pl

#### A.PL INTERNET S.A., Warsaw

Cracow Branch Manager

- Online A.pl store management,
- Management of dependent branch,
- Personnel management, organization of employees working time,
- Improving information about goods and magazine states in the branch,
- Supervision of the orders execution,
- Website administration,
- Implementation of sales plans,
- Car fleet management in the branch,

- Bookkeeping,
- Maintaining good relationships with business partners,,

### 2008.01 - 2008.04



## **Wydawnictwo Zielona Sowa, Cracow**

IT Specialist

- Helpdesk,
- Full service software and hardware,
- Website administration,
- Servers administration,
- Publishing materials archiving,
- Network configuration and administration,

# **LANGUAGES:**

English - B2, German - A1,

## **INTERESTS:**

- Playing guitar
- Historical Reenacting
- Vinyl Records